<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Management &#8211; Discy</title>
	<atom:link href="https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/question-category/management/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main</link>
	<description>Social Questions and Answers</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 01:18:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>I keep getting tasks that are above my skill level. How can I address this without coming accross as grossly incompetent?</title>
		<link>https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/question/i-keep-getting-tasks-that-are-above-my-skill-level-how-can-i-address-this-without-coming-accross-as-grossly-incompetent/</link>
					<comments>https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/question/i-keep-getting-tasks-that-are-above-my-skill-level-how-can-i-address-this-without-coming-accross-as-grossly-incompetent/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Aaron Aiken]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 01:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/questions/i-keep-getting-tasks-that-are-above-my-skill-level-how-can-i-address-this-without-coming-accross-as-grossly-incompetent/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I’m 6 months into a new job that uses a technology I’ve had no experience in (but am trying really hard to learn). Often I get tasks that I have real difficulty with. I flag this: I say that I’ve never done that before and I’ll have difficulty. I get some help, but the task [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I’m 6 months into a new job that uses a technology I’ve had no experience in (but am trying really hard to learn). Often I get tasks that I have real difficulty with. I flag this: I say that I’ve never done that before and I’ll have difficulty. I get some help, but the task always takes way longer than estimated and is done pretty badly. This puts me under a huge amount of stress and is embarrassing as my tasks often get rejected at QA.</p>
<p>I’m all for learning but its just too much. I need to master things incrementally, not all at once. Or else do a proper course on the subject.</p>
<p>How can I talk to my boss about this without looking like I’m useless or backing away from challenges?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/question/i-keep-getting-tasks-that-are-above-my-skill-level-how-can-i-address-this-without-coming-accross-as-grossly-incompetent/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dealing with an employee that went over my head</title>
		<link>https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/question/dealing-with-an-employee-that-went-over-my-head/</link>
					<comments>https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/question/dealing-with-an-employee-that-went-over-my-head/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Hope]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 01:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/questions/dealing-with-an-employee-that-went-over-my-head/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I manage a small team and recently hired for a new position. In the job posting it clearly stated that the work hours are from 8:00-4:30. No concerns about these hours were mentioned during the interview process at all. Recently after accepting the job offer, the new hire expressed an issue with the hours of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I manage a small team and recently hired for a new position. In the job posting it clearly stated that the work hours are from 8:00-4:30. No concerns about these hours were mentioned during the interview process at all.</p>
<p>Recently after accepting the job offer, the new hire expressed an issue with the hours of work, and proposed their own hours. The hours were not even consistent every day, they requested different work hours for each day of the week (they did all add up to the same total number of hours). I rejected this request.</p>
<p>The employee(before the first day of work), then emailed my superior with the same request and was approved.</p>
<p>How do I carry on managing an employee that is willing to go right over my head on an issue like this? How do I address this with my manager so that it doesn’t happen again. ( the first words out of my managers mouth should have been “Have you discyed this with your direct manager first?” )</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2code.info/demo/themes/Discy/Main/question/dealing-with-an-employee-that-went-over-my-head/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
